<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<quotelist>
 
  <quote id="1">
      <title>Whether you think you can, or you think you can't - you're right.</title>
      <author>Henry Ford</author>
  </quote>
 
  <quote id="2">
      <title>Becoming is better than being.</title>
      <author>Carol Dweck</author>    
  </quote>
 
  <quote id="3">
      <title>The sun himself is weak when he first rises, and gathers strength and courage as the day gets on.</title>
      <author>Charles Dickens</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="4">
      <title>How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world.</title>
      <author>Anne Frank</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="5">
      <title>If I had nine hours to chop down a tree, I'd spend the first six sharpening my axe.</title>
      <author>Abraham Lincoln</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="6">
      <title>The mind is its own place, and in itself can make a heaven of hell, a hell of heaven.</title>
      <author>John Milton</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="7">
      <title>Intelligence is the ability to adapt to change.</title>
      <author>Stephen Hawking</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="8">
      <title>Leaders can let you fail and yet not let you be a failure.</title>
      <author>Stanley McChrystal</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="9">
      <title>Talent wins games, but teamwork and intelligence wins championships.</title>
      <author>Michael Jordan</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="10">
      <title>There will be little rubs and disappointments everywhere, and we are all apt to expect too much; but then, if one scheme of happiness fails, human nature turns to another; if the first calculation is wrong, we make a second better: we find comfort somewhere.</title>
      <author>Jane Austen</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="11">
      <title>Be men, or be more than men. Be steady to your purposes and firm as a rock. This ice is not made of such stuff as your hearts may be; it is mutable and cannot withstand you if you say that it shall not.</title>
      <author>Mary Shelley</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="12">
      <title>Always be a first-rate version of yourself, instead of a second-rate version of somebody else.</title>
      <author>Judy Garland</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="13">
      <title>The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible.</title>
      <author>Charles Kingsleigh</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="14">
      <title>When we strive to become better than we are, everything around us becomes better too.</title>
      <author>Paulo Coelho</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="15">
      <title>We must believe that we are gifted for something and that this thing must be attained.</title>
      <author>Marie Curie</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="16">
      <title>Intelligence without ambition is a bird without wings.</title>
      <author>Salvador Dali</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="17">
      <title>If something is wrong, fix it now. But train yourself not to worry, worry fixes nothing.</title>
      <author>Ernest Hemingway</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="18">
      <title>Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant.</title>
      <author>Robert Louis Stevenson</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="19">
      <title>You have brains in your head. You have feet in your shoes. You can steer yourself any direction you choose. You're on your own. And you know what you know. And YOU are the one who'll decide where to go...</title>
      <author>Dr. Suess</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="20">
      <title>Innovation distinguishes from a leader and a follower.</title>
      <author>Steve Jobs</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="21">
      <title>The moment you doubt whether you can fly, you cease forever to be able to do it.</title>
      <author>J.M. Barrie</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="22">
      <title>There is only one way to avoid criticism. Do nothing. Be nothing. Say nothing.</title>
      <author>Aristotle</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="23">
      <title>If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader.</title>
      <author>John Quincy Adams</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="24">
      <title>Someone, at some point, came up with this very bad idea that an ordinary individual couldn't make a difference in the world. I think that's just a horrible thing.</title>
      <author>John Skoll</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="25">
      <title>If you hire people just because they can do a job, they'll work for your money. But if you hire people who believe what you believe, they'll work for you with blood and sweat and tears.</title>
      <author>Simon Sinek</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="26">
      <title>Success is the result of perfection, hard work, learning from failure, loyalty, and persistence.</title>
      <author>Colin Powell</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="27">
      <title>The three great essentials to achieve anything worthwhile are, first, hard work; second, stick-to-itiveness; third, common sense.</title>
      <author>Thomas A. Edison</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="28">
      <title>Developing a good work ethic is key. Apply yourself at whatever you do, whether you're a janitor or taking your first summer job, because that work ethic will be reflected in everything you do in life.</title>
      <author>Tyler Perry</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="29">
      <title>The only way to do great work is to love what you do. If you havn't found it yet, keep looking. Don't settle.</title>
      <author>Steve Jobs</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="30">
      <title>It's easy to solve a problem that everyone sees, but it's hard to solve a problem that almost no one sees.</title>
      <author>Tony Fadell</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="31">
      <title>Learning never exhausts the mind.</title>
      <author>Leonardo Da Vinci</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="32">
      <title>My mother said to me, "If you are a soldier, you will become a general. If you are a monk, you will become the Pope." Instead, I was a painter, and became Picasso.</title>
      <author>Pablo Picasso</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="33">
      <title>Never ruin an apology with an excuse.</title>
      <author>Benjamin Franklin</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="34">
      <title>Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it.</title>
      <author>Dwight D. Eisenhower</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="35">
      <title>There are no two words in the English language more harmful than "good job."</title>
      <author>Terence Fletcher</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="36">
      <title>I am not a product of my circumstances. I am a product of my decisions.</title>
      <author>Stephen Covey</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="37">
      <title>You can't change how people treat you or what they say about you. All you can do is change how you react to it.</title>
      <author>Mahatma Gandhi</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="38">
      <title>Do you want to know who you are? Don't ask. Act! Action will delineate and define you.</title>
      <author>Thomas Jefferson</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="39">
      <title>The man who moves a mountain begins by carrying away small stones. </title>
      <author>Confucius</author>    
  </quote>

  <quote id="40">
      <title>Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn.</title>
      <author>Benjamin Franklin</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="41">
      <title>If you hear a voice within you say "you cannot paint," then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced.</title>
      <author>Vincent Van Gogh</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="42">
      <title>Don't limit yourself. Many people limit themselves to what they think they can do. You can go as far as your mind lets you. What you believe, remember, you can achieve.</title>
      <author>Mary Kay Ash</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="43">
      <title>Success is a lousy teacher. It seduces smart people into thinking they can't lose.</title>
      <author>Bill Gates</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="44">
      <title>A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.</title>
      <author>Winston Churchill</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="45">
      <title>You just have to keep driving down the road. It's going to bend and curve and you'll speed up and slow down, but the road keeps going.</title>
      <author>Ellen DeGeneres</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="46">
      <title>If you don't stand for something, you'll fall for anything.</title>
      <author>Malcolm X</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="47">
      <title>We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence then, is not an act, but a habit.</title>
      <author>Aristotle</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="48">
      <title>Believe in yourself. Never bend your head. Hold it high. Look the world straight in the eye.</title>
      <author>Helen Keller</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="49">
      <title>Try not to become a man of success but rather try to become a man of value.</title>
      <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="50">
      <title>Nothing is impossible, the word itself says, "I'm possible!"</title>
      <author>Audrey Hepburn</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="51">
      <title>The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step.</title>
      <author>Lao Tzu</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="52">
      <title>You must learn from the mistakes of others. You can't possibly live long enough to make them all yourself.</title>
      <author>Sam Levenson</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="53">
      <title>Every experience in your life is being orchestrated to teach you something you need to know to move forward.</title>
      <author>Brian Tracy</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="54">
      <title>Accept responsibility for your life. Know that it is you who will get you where you want to go, no one else.</title>
      <author>Les Brown</author>
  </quote>

  <quote id="55">
      <title>Anyone who has never made a mistake has never tried anything new.</title>
      <author>Albert Einstein</author>
  </quote>
</quotelist>